http://www.mysportsite.com/privacy

Select Your Currency:
Create Free Trial
Privacy StatementLooking for a team website for your team? Learn more about mySportSite and start building your own!
Information Collection and Use
Tilted Pixel Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Tilted Pixel Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Organizations
In order to use this website, an organization must first complete the registration form. During registration the organization is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. The organization name and website provided in the form will be shown publicly on our website. However the contact name, phone number and email address will not.
Individuals
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. This information will not be sold to any third parties. Any information collected on a custom form on a mySportSite Website is the property of the organization that licenses that website. The information you provide there is subject to that organization's privacy policy, not ours.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a username more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to save personal settings such as username or currency. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. If we partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tilted Pixel Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys and Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal/zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to support@mysportsite.com
Site and Service Updates
We may send the user important site and service announcement updates. These notices are designed to inform users of important changes to the mySportSite Websites/Services and thus there is not an opt-out option.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your telephone number), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support at support@mysportsite.com
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: Tilted Pixel Inc.383030-256 King St N Waterloo, Ontario N2J 4T9 support@mysportsite.comP: 1-866-749-2673
© 2003 - 2020 mySportSite Inc. All rights reserved.
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Statement
mySportSite Inc.
Phone: 519-772-6887
Toll Free: 1-866-749-2673
Email: support@mysportsite.com
Waterloo, Ontario, Canada
All prices in US Dollars.
Canadian Dollars
